Guide to the Forest Hills Gardens Corporation Records, 1922-1979, 1922-1958 (bulk)
Forest Hills Gardens Corporation Records
- Alphabetical Files
  - 1930-1934
    - 1933
      - Certificates, 1928, 1931 (Box 31)
      - Committee Reports, 1933 (Box 31)
        Law, architecture, annual meeting
      - D - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - E - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - F - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - First Church of Christ Scientist, 1929-1934 (Box 31)
        Regarding wall construction and roofing tile
      - Forest Hills Dwellings, Inc. - McAvoy, 1933 (Box 31)
        D. McAvoy, an officer of Bloodgood Real Estate, developers, 1928-1929
      - G - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Gibson, ca. 1930-1933 (Box 5)
        Memoranda and correspondence from E.O. Gibson, (presumably FHG office employee) and other correspondence
      - H - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Hanavan (Director), 1931-1934 (Box 31)
        Includes clippings
      - Insurance, 1933 (Box 31)
        Policies, claims
      - J - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Mr. Knight (Director), 1929-1931 (Box 31)
      - K - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - L - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Lampposts, street signs, 1934 (Box 31)
        Claims, repairs
      - M - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Mr. Moore (Director), 1932-1933 (Box 31)
      - N - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1933 (Box 31)
      - O - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Orders & Invoices, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Q - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - P - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - R - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - S - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Mr. Speir (Director), 1933-1934 (Box 31)
      - Streets, 1930-1934 (Box 31)
        Regarding paving, closing, etc. - excerpts from minutes of Director's Meetings bearing upon streets in FHG showing a history of consistent and consecutive maintenance of streets and claimed ownership by FHGC from Jan. 1, 1923 to Aug. 1932 (25 pages)
      - T - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Mr. Teague (Director), 1933 (Box 31)
      - Trial Balance, 1933 (Box 31)
        Ledger sheets
      - Treasurer's Report, 1933 (Box 31)
        Bookkeeping details and audit
      - U - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Upkeep Committee Reports, 1933 (Box 31)
        Reports, specs, inventories, costs
      - V - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - W - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1933 (Box 31)
        Agreements of various homeowners
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 31)
    - 1934
      - A - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Arrears, 1934 (Box 14)
      - B - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Judge Boyce (Director), 1934 (Box 14)
      - C - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Committee Reports, 1934 (Box 14)
        Law, Architecture, Annual Meeting
      - D - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - E - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - F - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - G - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - H - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - I - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Insurance, 1934 (Box 14)
      - J - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - K - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - L - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Lampposts, 1933 (Box 14)
        Street signs, claims, correspondence
      - M - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - N - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1934-1938 (Box 14)
      - O - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Orders & Invoices, 1934 (Box 14)
      - P - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Q - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - R - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - S - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Streets, 1934 (Box 14)
        Regarding buses, closings (many photos), naming of Station Square
      - T - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Taxpayers Association, 1934 (Box 14)
        Relating to overvaluation of property of values for tax purposes, 1921-1935; report of organizational meeting; 1932, Constitution and By-Laws
      - Teague, 1934 (Box 22)
        An architect
      - Treasurers Reports, 1934 (Box 14)
        Bookkeeping details and Audit
      - Trial Balance - Ledger sheets, 1934 (Box 14)
      - U - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1934 (Box 14)
        Costs, worksheets, reports, inventories, payrolls, Dutch Elm disease, new Burns Street sewer contract, survey of FHG streets: types, present conditions and requirements
      - V - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - W - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 14)
      - Woodward (Director), 1934 (Box 14)
  - 1935-1939
    - 1935
      - B - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 11)
      - Block 12 -, 1931-1937 (Box 11)
        Development of Block 12 (now Leslie Apartments.) - includes sketches of original G. Atterbury concept of apartment building
      - Boyce, 1935 (Box 11)
      - Bus Petitions, 1935-1936 (Box 12)
        To bar buses from FHG
      - C - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 11)
      - Committee Reports, 1935 (Box 11)
        Corporation Committees and Minutes of Annual Meeting
      - D - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 11)
      - E - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 11)
      - Earle, 1935 (Box 11)
        Projects of Mr. Earle, a builder and developer
      - F - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - G - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Gardens Corp. Permits to Open Streets, 1925-1939 (Box 11)
      - H - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - I - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Insurance, 1935 (Box 12)
      - J - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - K - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - L - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Lampposts, 1935 (Box 12)
        Damage claims, orders for new posts
      - M - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - N - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - O - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Orders, 1935 (Box 12)
        Receipts, estimates
      - P - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - R - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - S - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Streets, 1935 (Box 12)
        Use of streets, permits, complaints about buses
      - T - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Treasurers Reports, 1935 (Box 12)
        Accounts, inventories, receipts, expenses, reports, audit
      - Trial Balance, 1935 (Box 12)
        Work sheets for Treasurers Report
      - U - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1935 (Box 12)
        Reports, catalog, correspondence regarding maintenance, demolition of Hanks House in Block 12
      - V - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - W - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1935 (Box 12)
        Modification agreements with various property owners
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 12)
    - 1936
      - A - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Arrears, 1936 (Box 13)
        Foreclosures, delinquent accounts
      - B - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Boyce, 1936 (Box 13)
        Correspondence of Law Committee - beginnings of Block 12 controversy
      - C - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Committee Reports and Minutes of Board Meeting, 1936 (Box 13)
      - D - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Dartt (Director), 1936 (Box 13)
      - E - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Earle, 1936 (Box 13)
        Builder and developer, regarding various projects
      - F - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - G - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - H - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - I - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Insurance, 1936 (Box 13)
        Regarding various claims and policies
      - J - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - K - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - L - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Lampposts, 1936 (Box 13)
        Estimates, catalogs, invoices, claims for damage
      - M - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - N - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - O - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Orders & Receipts, 1936 (Box 13)
      - P - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - Printing, 1936 (Box 13)
        Reprint from New York Times regarding handbill advertising (nuisance)
      - Publicity Book, 1936 (Box 13)
        Correspondence and working papers for proposed publicity booklet regarding FHG by Mr. M. M. Davidson, a Director and former President. (no finished copies found) was to contain photographs
      - Q - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - R - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 13)
      - S - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 14)
      - Sewers, 1923-1937 (Box 14)
        Problems and proposed additions to sewer system suggested because of proposed new addition to Forest Hills Inn ( 1937 ) - In addition, surveys and reports dealing with adequacy of system as new building proceeded
      - Streets, 1936 (Box 14)
        Paving (some photos), complaints, use of street (celebrations), numbering of houses
      - Trial Balance, 1936 (Box 14)
      - Treasurers Reports, 1936 (Box 14)
        Audit, Statements of Income, expenses, cash, work sheets, inventories
      - T - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 28)
      - U - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 28)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1936 (Box 28)
        Bills and reports regarding maintenance
      - V - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 28)
      - V - Vanderveer - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 28)
        Regarding Vanderveer land in Stafford Avenue between Groton and Harrow Streets
      - W - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 28)
      - W - Vanderveer, 1936 (Box 28)
        Correspondence regarding Vanderveer land
    - 1937
      - A - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 3)
      - Atterbury, 1937-1938 (Box 5)
        Correspondence regarding architectural matters and problems of maintaining standards
      - Arrears, 1937 (Box 3)
        Larger folder of correspondence regarding arrears of maintenance changes
      - B - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 3)
      - Boundary Markers, 1938 (Box 3)
        Contracts for boundaries posts at Burns St., Markwood Road and Union Turnpike
      - Boyce, 1937 (Box 3)
        Law committee reports and correspondence
      - C - Reports, 1937 (Box 5)
      - Committee Reports - Monthly and annual meetings, 1937 (Box 5)
      - D - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 5)
        Includes a letter regarding curb boxes
      - Mr. Daniels (President of FHG corp.) - Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 5)
      - Mr. Davidson - Correspondence with Mr. D. - a director of Gardens Corp. (Box 5)
      - E - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 5)
      - Earle, 1937 (Box 5)
        Regarding fences in his property
      - F - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 5)
      - Four Mills Agreements, Oct. 1, 1923 (Box 5)
        Increase from 2 to 4 mills maintenance charge (4 copies)
      - I - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 5)
      - J - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 5)
      - K - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 5)
      - A.L. Kochar (Box 5)
        Regarding his architectural requests
      - L - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 4)
      - Lampposts, 1937 (Box 5)
        Correspondence regarding replacement of damaged lampposts
      - Long Island Rail Road, 1935 (Box 5)
        Problems with Brodsky News Service - paper delivery truck parking under F.F. Bridge and Continental Air, also fence work and maintenance of steps, etc.
      - M - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 4)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 4)
      - N - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 4)
      - O - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 4)
      - Orders and Correspondence with vendors, 1937 (Box 4)
      - P - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
      - Parks, 1937 (Box 9)
        Park records for 1937, and correspondence
      - Q - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
      - R - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
      - S - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
      - Seward, a director, 1936-1937, 1936 (Box 9)
      - Sincerbeaux, F.H. (director) (Box 9)
      - Streets, 1937 (Box 9)
        Correspondence regarding sewers, closings, traffic, paving, buses
      - T - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
      - Treasurers Reports - Bookkeeping and audit, 1937 (Box 9)
      - Trial Balance - Bookkeeping ledger sheets, 1937 (Box 9)
      - U - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
      - Upkeep Committee Reports, 1937 (Box 9)
        Payrolls, time sheets, inventories
      - V - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
      - W - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
      - Waivers of Restrictions - Agreements with various homeowners, 1937 (Box 9)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 9)
    - 1938
      - A - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 9)
      - Annual Meeting - Address of President and committee report, 1938 (Box 5)
      - B - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 9)
      - Committee Reports, 1938 (Box 9)
        Architecture, law, annual meeting
      - Boyce, 1938 (Box 9)
        Law committee correspondence, and correspondence
      - C - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 9)
      - Collection of Maintenance Charges, ca. 1938 (Box 9)
        Arrears from Judge Boyce's files (some prior)
      - D - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 9)
      - Davidson, Morris, a director 1938-1943, 1938 (Box 9)
      - E - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 9)
      - F - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 9)
      - G - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 9)
      - H - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 9)
      - Home Owners Loan Corp. (Box 9)
        Correspondence with HOLC (which owned several FHG homes) regarding dues, maintenance of property
      - I - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - Insurance, 1938 (Box 9)
        Policies, claims, misc. correspondence
      - J - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - K - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - L - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - Lampposts, 1938 (Box 4)
        Replacement of lampposts due to accidents and vandalism
      - M - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - N - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - O - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - Orders & Vendors, 1938 (Box 4)
      - P - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - Parks Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
        Samples of park cards and lists of owners
      - Q - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - R - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - S - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 4)
      - Sincerbeaux, Mr. S. (director), 1938 (Box 3)
      - Streets, 1938 (Box 4)
        Larger folder regarding petition to alter bus routes (Triboro Coach Corp.), correspondence regarding Good Humor trucks, Topographical Bureau (opening of streets and curb cuts - city wanted "curb fees"), paving complaints - closed streets 1938 (photos), and misc. correspondence regarding title to streets, buses
      - T - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 22)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1938 (Box 22)
        Balance sheets
      - Trial Balance, 1938 (Box 22)
        Handwritten sheets
      - U - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 22)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1938 (Box 22)
        Vouchers, time sheets, inventories
      - V - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 22)
      - W - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 22)
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1938 (Box 22)
        Also list of waivers 1928-1931
    - 1939
      - A - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
        Also a list ( Apr. 13, 1939 ) of photographs of Gardens with index numbers: Station Square, Streets and Eleves, Gateways and Doorways, Lanterns and Street Signs, Parks, Church-in-Gardens, July 4 celebration
      - Adsit Reports, August 14-25, 1939 (Box 23)
        Office activity sheets, itemized (Mrs. Carl Adsit)
      - B - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - Block 12, 1937 (Box 23)
        Matters pertaining to development of Block 12 apartment (Atterbury correspondence) The Leslie
      - Boyce, 1939 (Box 23)
        Law committee reports 1939; change of name from Gardens Corp, to FHG Corp.; President's address 1939 annual meeting
      - C - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - E.W. Clark (Director), 1933-1939 (Box 23)
      - Committee Reports, 1939 (Box 23)
        Reports on various committees
      - D - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - E - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - F - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - Freak Letters (Box 23)
      - G - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - H - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - Hawkins, Glenwood, 1939 (Box 23)
        Regarding arrears
      - Hill, T.C., 1938 (Box 23)
      - Insurance, 1939 (Box 23)
        Includes policies and liability claims
      - J - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - K - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 23)
      - Kay, F.C., 1938 (Box 16)
        Regarding maintenance charges
      - L - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
      - Lampposts, 1939 (Box 16)
        Regarding damaged lampposts (accident), letter to Mr. Webb (probably misfiled), correspondence regarding lighting
      - Latshaw, 1939 (Box 16)
        Lawsuit regarding tenant's violation, also candy manufacturing and other violations of covenants and restrictions
      - M - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
      - N - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
        "N" owners - letter referring to maintenance of street lights from N.Y. and Queens Electric Light and Power CO.
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1939 (Box 16)
        Especially World's Fair and Japanese beetles
      - O - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
      - Orders, 1939 (Box 16)
        Orders for spraying addressograph plates, street signs and associated correspondence with vendors
      - P - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
        Includes a list of proxies for Annual Meeting
      - Parks, 1939 (Box 16)
        Park card records (admissions cards), agreements modifying covenants with individual owners
      - Proxy - Letters - Sic (Box 16)
      - Q - - Complaint from Mrs. Quillin (1 pc.), 1939 (Box 16)
      - R - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
        Especially welcoming letters and architectural permits
      - Rooming houses, 1939 (Box 16)
        Especially with regard to World's Fair
      - S - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
        Mainly architectural matters
      - Streets, 1939 (Box 16)
        Sewer connections, Triboror Coach Corp. bus routes - photos "private streets closed" and paving pictures (Tarvia lithic) changes in street names - Nuden Rd., Whitson, etc. changed to numbered streets in city maps made by topographic bureau - proposed uniformity vetoed by Mayn (la G.) especially Tennis Place (Tennis Road)
      - T - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
        Architectural matters
      - Taxpayers Association, 1935-1939 (Box 16)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1939 (Box 16)
        Monthly balance sheets and expenses
      - Trial Balance, 1939 (Box 16)
        Handwritten balance sheets
      - U - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 16)
        Welcoming letter to Roderick Fields as a member of Gardens Corp. - and reply with thanks (2 sheets of papers in this file)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1939 (Box 16)
        Monthly reports, correspondence
      - Valiquette garage request, 1939 (Box 16)
      - W - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 16)
        complaints, requests
  - 1940-1944
    - 1940
      - A - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Adair Reports, July 1940 (Box 6)
        Office daily log by A. Adair, possibly a summer replacement for Laura Freeman
      - B - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Judge Boyce - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
        Pres. FHGC and Law Committee Reports
      - C - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Committee Reports - Law and Architecture, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Community House, 1926 (Box 6)
        Papers relating to fund-raising to build, by-laws, preamble, organization, newspaper clippings, brochure, Souvenir Program of the Opening August, 12, 13, 14, 1926 (Atterbury Architect)
      - D - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - E - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - F - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - G - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - H - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Help - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
        Regarding employees, especially summer
      - I - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Insurance -, 1940 (Box 6)
        Policies, contracts, correspondence, claims
      - J - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - K - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - L - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Lampposts, 1940 (Box 6)
        ( June 1939, and 1941 ) - regarding repairs, replacements, requests for additional lighting and letter from NYC - Dept. WSGE regarding assumption of energy costs for street lighting
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Mr. Moore - Correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 6)
      - N - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Newspaper Clippings relating to FHG, 1940 (Box 6)
      - O - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Orders, 1940 (Box 6)
        Office equipment, plant equipment and services of private contractors
      - P - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Parks, 1940 (Box 6)
      - R - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Reydel, William (director), 1940 (Box 6)
      - S - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 6)
      - Sheets, 1940 (Box 6)
        Correspondence regarding curb cuts, tree removal, street closing, use by buses, paving sewer connections, renaming of 77th Road to Wendover Road (copy of Local Law in City Record)
      - T - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 22)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 1940 (Box 22)
      - Trial Balance, 1940 (Box 22)
      - U - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 22)
      - Upkeep Committee, 1940 (Box 22)
        News entries, reports
      - V - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 22)
      - W - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 22)
      - Waivers of Restrictions, 1940 (Box 22)
      - XYZ - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 22)
      - Zoning, 1935-1940 (Box 22)
        City Planning Commission, Board Estimates, correspondence
    - 1941
      - A - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - B - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Block 12, 1940 (Box 7)
        Correspondence pertaining to "The Leslie" apartment houses then under construction
      - Boyce - Law Committee Reports, 1941 (Box 7)
      - C - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Committee Reports, 1941 (Box 7)
        FHG minutes, annual meeting minutes, Architecture Committee (esp. regarding Block 12 - the Leslie)
      - D - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Defense Committee, 1941 (Box 7)
        Regarding WWII preparedness i.e.: air raid shelters, emergency medical facilities, home defense
      - E - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - F - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Freak Letters, 1941 (Box 7)
      - G - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Gump, Gladys Lusk, 134 Ascan Avenue, 1941 (Box 7)
        Roaming house affair
      - H - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Help, 1941 (Box 7)
        Personnel, especially temporary
      - Hager, Theo W. - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - I - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Insurance - Claims, policies, correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - J - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - K - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Kiendl (director), 1936-1940 (Box 7)
      - L - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Lampposts - Damage, replacements, 1941 (Box 7)
      - M - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Mc - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - McMulin (director), 1941 (Box 7)
      - Moore - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - N - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - News of Forest Hills Gardens Corporation - Work in design of new Bulletin (Box 7)
      - O - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Orders - Office, plant maintenance, 1941 (Box 7)
      - P - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Parks - Maintenance, security, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Publicity, 1941 (Box 7)
        Press releases to local papers, especially FH-KG Post regarding current events
      - R - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - S - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 7)
      - Seward (director), 1938-1941 (Box 7)